<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cornhuskers on Collin Hansen&#39;s Github Site</title>
    <link>/tags/cornhuskers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cornhuskers on Collin Hansen&#39;s Github Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/cornhuskers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How Important was Ndamukong Suh To The Nebraska Defense?</title>
      <link>/2021/04/25/how-important-was-ndamukong-suh-to-the-nebraska-defense/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/04/25/how-important-was-ndamukong-suh-to-the-nebraska-defense/</guid>
      <description>Ndamukong Suh was, and still is, a force to be reckoned with on the football field. He was one of the most dominant college players to ever play his position, and has carried that legacy with him into the NFL. Opposing teams feared him during his time at Nebraska. Opposing offensive lineman were petrified heading into their games against Nebraska, scrambling their minds trying to figure out any way to stop Suh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it time to jump ship on Scott Frost?</title>
      <link>/2021/04/04/is-it-time-to-jump-ship-on-scott-frost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/04/04/is-it-time-to-jump-ship-on-scott-frost/</guid>
      <description>Nebraska football has arguably the most loyal fans in all of college athletics. The sense of pride in their football program is no different. Fans of Nebraska will support the team until the day they die, but many have begun to lose hope in Scott Frost returning the team to glory. Scott Frost is the hometown hero that came back to Nebraska and won a national championship, and he’s the one that came back to Nebraska yet again to try and help them win even more as a coach.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
